Apart from that,
بعيدا عن هذا،
you really didn't remember anything?
هل حقا لم تتذكر شيئا؟
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I'll trust you for now.
سوف أثق بك في الوقت الراهن.
But I finally know your background.
لكنني أخيرًا أعرف خلفيتك.
This is not comfortable.
هذا غير مريح.
How...
كيف...
Why can't you take off your clothes?
لماذا لا تستطيع خلع ملابسك؟
I will find you a dress.
سوف أجد لك فستانا.
Why is she blushing again?
لماذا احمرار خجلا مرة أخرى؟
It shouldn't be hard to look at him in this clothes.
لا ينبغي أن يكون من الصعب النظر إليه بهذه الملابس.
Should I make it a rule not to take off clothes
هل يجب أن أجعل من عدم خلع الملابس قاعدة؟
not taking off clothes randomly?
عدم خلع الملابس بشكل عشوائي؟
The tailor makes the man.
الخياط يصنع الرجل .
The tailor makes the horse.
الخياط يصنع الحصان .
It's so pretty.
انها جميلة جدا.
If we change him to be bossy by programming,
إذا قمنا بتغييره ليكون متسلطا عن طريق البرمجة،
jin Mulai.
بداية الجني.
You can learn everything, right?
يمكنك أن تتعلم كل شيء، أليس كذلك؟
Certainly.
بالتأكيد.
Woman,
امرأة،
you can only use my card.
يمكنك فقط استخدام بطاقتي.
Sister,
أخت،
I have been waiting for you for a long time.
لقد كنت أنتظرك لفترة طويلة.
Don't be tired.
لا تتعب.
I'll feel bad for you.
سوف أشعر بالسوء بالنسبة لك.
What if you learn to be a domineering president?
ماذا لو تعلمت أن تكون رئيسًا مستبدًا؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
This is
هذا هو
how incredible.
كيف لا يصدق.
The women on your Earth
النساء على أرضك
prefer men like this.
تفضل الرجال مثل هذا.
I am testing you, okay?
أنا أختبرك، حسنًا؟
Tell me now.
أخبرني الآن.
Can you learn from it?
هل يمكنك التعلم منه؟
Could you let me learn something good?
هل يمكن أن تسمح لي بتعلم شيء جيد؟
Think about it.
فكر في الأمر.
The money that you owe me,
المال الذي تدين به لي،
alright?
على ما يرام؟
Done.
منتهي.
Activate Alpha Mode.
تفعيل وضع ألفا.
Woman,
امرأة،
your caught my attention.
لقد لفتت انتباهي.
My goodness.
رباه.
You entered the state so soon.
لقد دخلت الدولة بهذه السرعة.
Woman.
امرأة.
Are you playing with fire?
هل تلعب بالنار؟
Hold on.
يتمسك.
This is not the script I asked for.
هذا ليس النص الذي طلبته.
You're putting on an act?
أنت تقوم بعمل ما؟
How can my woman
كيف يمكن لامرأة بلدي
a woman like me can't walk on her own feet?
امرأة مثلي لا تستطيع المشي على قدميها؟
That's a shameful line.
وهذا خط مخجل.
However,
لكن،
I like that.
أحب ذلك.
Why am I seeing these?
لماذا أرى هؤلاء؟
He's still a baby.
انه لا يزال طفلا.
Help
يساعد
oh, my goodness.
يا إلهي.
I haven't seen him for just a few days,
لم أره منذ بضعة أيام فقط،
why is he suddenly paralyzed?
لماذا أصيب بالشلل فجأة؟
Come on.
تعال.
That's not true.
هذا ليس صحيحا.
Put me down.
انزلني.
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
Hold me tight.
مسكني بقوة.
Woman.
امرأة.
Drink more hot water.
شرب المزيد من الماء الساخن.
Slowly.
ببطء.
Don't burn yourself.
لا تحرق نفسك.
Come on.
تعال.
Sample.
عينة.
I don't believe I can't cure you.
لا أعتقد أنني لا أستطيع علاجك.
That's enough.
هذا يكفي.
If this goes on,
إذا استمر هذا،
I have osteoporosis at such a young age.
أعاني من هشاشة العظام في مثل هذه السن المبكرة.
I'm sick of it.
أنا مريض منه.
I can't eat this industrial saccharin anymore.
لا أستطيع أكل هذا السكرين الصناعي بعد الآن.
Please stop hugging me.
من فضلك توقف عن عناقي.
What old-fashioned trick is he playing again?
ما هي الخدعة القديمة التي يلعبها مرة أخرى؟
Brother.
أخ.
Can't you play by common sense?
ألا يمكنك اللعب بالفطرة السليمة؟
You're wrong.
أنت مخطئ.
Come again.
تعال مرة أخرى.
I don't know if she likes that overbearing president.
لا أعرف إذا كانت تحب ذلك الرئيس المتعجرف.
She is using a cruel trick.
إنها تستخدم خدعة قاسية.
Who can stand it?
من يستطيع تحمله؟
Sleep mode.
وضع السكون.
[Loading]
[تحميل]
Once in the bossy boss,
مرة واحدة في رئيسه متسلط،
I'll never like the overbearing president again.
لن أحب الرئيس المتعجرف مرة أخرى.
It seems that
يبدو أن
the league has sent another alien to take me back.
أرسل الدوري كائنًا فضائيًا آخر لإعادتي.
I need to finish the task my grandpa entrusted me with.
يجب أن أنهي المهمة التي أوكلها لي جدي.
What else are you hiding from me?
ماذا تخفي عني؟
I hope that guy
أتمنى ذلك الرجل
won't cause me any more trouble.
لن يسبب لي المزيد من المتاعب
A safe landing.
هبوط آمن.
Arrive at the earth safely.
الوصول إلى الأرض بسلام.